Yeah, you owe me. Oh
Here I'm looking for my vape and it's right there. Yeah, damn. I'm a fucking guitar
It was sitting next to me the whole time
My one died and the one that was charged was right here. I'm good. I'm looking under the chair
I'm looking in the seat cushions. That was right there. Let's see
He said he got door knocks today. It's still happening. Well, I assume it's probably not gonna get any better
Like he's new stream title. I've had enough. I'm not dr. Phil. Oh
No, remember your Howard Stern, buddy. You're Howard Stern. So
You wanted this you wanted to fucking
Go against the grain and not listen to people who had genuine fucking feedback for you
People who and I mean there's people not just me, but there's people who who like the guy
Who are trying to tell him and he just
Doesn't get it doesn't care. He has no morals. Well, guess what people around here have morals
We might be pieces of shit and assholes, but there's still a moral compass and when you
Want to platform?
Someone like Brandon Q and choose the shit all over people who supported you. This is what you get
We all watched live Psyche react to Benny hitting his mother and Psyche said he didn't hit her the guy is delusional
And he watched it said he didn't hit her. What did he say? He said, oh he pushed her or something and then um
Fucking the only time he got upset after watching all that then watch Benny scream at his mom while we were live
He was calling her a fucking bitch or whatever right live
But didn't care until the cat didn't came up and that bothered him
But it didn't bother him enough to stop talking to him because he was still glazing bunny days later
So big deal that was so everyone just celebrates him
I guess and so he's getting what he wants and you know, sometimes the bad guys win
you know, but
I'm gonna at least you know fight back as long as I can
With just the truth
I don't know. I guess nobody wants the truth. The truth is like the truth is ugly sometimes and
The lies are attractive and dressed, you know, and so
The truth is you're platforming a predator. That's the truth
Okay, right
I'm not trying to give you places to hang out trying to give like cool people
Yeah, I'll kick you out. I don't care. Kick that one out of chat. What'd they say Tony owns you boy
I heard people just harass me and shout all day. So that's not what it's about
You can go talk shit about me on Samman's panel. I try to give someone a place to kick hang out anywhere else
They like to immediately kick someone that person blocked and you know, these people that are like
Not even on camera, right? Okay
Choose your she's your side. It's fine. You want to choose side? You had a choice and he made a decision. Yeah
Oh, it's Amanda. I'm here to give like people that want to hang out like in a positive way, not harass me
IRL which is happening right now, right? Am I gonna give you guys a place to hang out? No, I'm gonna give you a quick ban
And then everyone else is like afraid. I know, you know
Sometimes like people that are like followers are afraid to talk afraid and it's like you're like, well
What's everyone gonna think what's I'm gonna say? I'm gonna ban from these chats and everything. Oh, I need to do nothing
I need to do nothing of the sort. I need to do nothing for you. Bye
All I need to do is kick you out of the chat
Go potty and I will and it's like, you know, it's good. Just reveal yourself and I'll just kick out of the tab
But if people that actually want to like talk and want to have fun
You know, you can say something and you can pretty much say anything you can say anything here except like fucking stuff about that person
Who's actually criminally harassing me and you're just an accomplice if you're participating in that so you're a criminal accomplice
criminal
Right. So you can see the people on the screen. You can see what their names are. Just watch out for those people. They're probably all the same person.
Yeah, but yeah, if no one's to support me anymore, well, they weren't really good friends in the first place.
No, they're just so willing to like, you know, especially if they so they aren't good friends in the first place.
If they aren't willing to stand by you while you platform and defend a fucking predator.
So in order to be a good friend, you have to turn a blind eye to supporting platforming and promoting a legit predator.
That's what a good friend does.
Okay.
What do you need help with, Ashante?
That's a good friend.
If you dig into things a little bit, beyond the surface level, you'll see what's really going on.
But no one wants to see the truth.
What's really going on?
The truth is, you know, a beautiful lie is more attractive than an ugly truth.
Sometimes the truth is ugly.
Sometimes you'll see, like, how misled you've been and, like, what's really going on.
But, sorry, I don't have beautiful truths for you here.
I have, like, you know, I just have the truth.
The truth is not really pretty right now, like, what's been going on.
The truth is not pretty, what's going on.
slander, smear campaigns, these ostracism campaigns.
Slander and spear campaigns.
I never tell you where to go or not to go.
You can go to anywhere you want.
I don't care.
I'm not allowed in most of these places anymore.
My voice has been silenced.
I can't go and beat his panel.
I can't go and beat his chat.
I can't go in Christine's chat.
I'm just not welcome in many places.
So I barely have my own show to go on right now.
But not one positive thing today.
Concrete Larry, yeah, see, I mean,
you guys can just see the concrete Larry, right?
You nasty Ashante.
No, I don't know why these people are in my chat
and like nobody else is, but yeah, just to scram
if you're like, I don't care if I have zero people here.
What's up, Brandon?
Oh, just fighting the good fight, you know.
Again, I'll stand up for truth.
Fighting the good fight, by the way.
The truth is, you know, and, you know,
just being harassed by this guy.
Finally.
All these all you can see on the screen what they've been saying 13 minutes in I oh, I must it's all it's all basically
1327 seconds in he has his first person chat and chat
psyche goes with who is
Drip feeding him money currently mayors and Brandon. He will stand on that hill until it stops being lucrative
bingo
We know who it is, but the chat will build up again. Like, you know, as soon as I can people figure out the truth
I'm sure then I'll be the most popular person, right? They are obsessed, right?
As soon as they figure out the truth, he'll be the most popular person. Oh, yeah, I don't have to keep anybody's name out of my mouth
Constantly constantly he's obsessed. I'm obsessed for over a year. He's been sending people to my house
Okay, and I'm obsessed and he's talking to me and chats and I'm obsessed. Okay. Go ahead
I mean, no, I mean, I mean, not you Brandon, but the person sucks to Sarah somewhere or whatever.
Sorry, I get something stuff, but
Yeah, I mean, it's a YouTube it has sort of the demonetizing everybody if they use like thumbnails
Generated by AI if they do anything with and even though YouTube has like all these AI tools that they were
It was used and warn anybody that just started demonetizing them kept their monthly money. They now they're demonetizing for AI thumbnails
Buddy, I don't think that's why you're demonetized. They're sweet cheeks, but
Go ahead and blame it on that
Alex has one person in her chat guess who it is Brandon
Apparently Brandon Q showed them DMs that look like it had extremely obvious edits. Oh, yeah, it's used. Um, oh
God, what's the name of the app? It's an app?
Mockley or something like that
It's an app used to make fake DMs from all types of platforms.
I think it's called Mockly.
No, I'm not judging you.
I'm not judging you.
Try a bath.
I don't know.
I'm sorry for your discharge.
What else did they do?
Oh, then they started putting ads on my content,
which I never had before.
I always had the option not to put any ads,
but I guess they wanted to put ads on my content
the whole time.
So why are they saying that it's not worthy or whatever?
And then they're putting ads on it now.
I didn't have ads on it before.
All I had was a membership going on.
And they shut down the membership.
And it's like pretty frustrating, right?
And then you're listening to anybody
that wants to flag the channel, you know?
And so I'm just over at this little,
kind of my safer channel right now.
Who smokes cigars like cigarettes that these like hate watchers over? Oh, can you imagine the smell of that apartment?
Nasty smoke fucking
cat piss and shit
B.O. Blegh
Like you know
Kind of on me tattletail and stuff over every little thing for not even stuff. I'm doing it's like people on the panel
It's dangerous running panels. I know it's fucking
Not my link of
But um yeah before I get like too impressed about it probably just there's Sarah summer she gets banned because she mentioned Tony
Cannot man. Why don't you just block Tony's name coward?
Toxic at this point. It's like, you know, it's I don't want to be under stress
I like to be happy in a good mood. You know, I'll finally have a
There's a nice person down and like lying about me, you know and attacking me
It's like, you know, maybe I'll go like build up my rumble go build up my kick
I'll go build up my twitch. I'll go build up my others my other channels where it's like
Oh, even my tiktok where I get a lot of love instead of just like
Yeah, I just have to keep going but you know, I've got down it's like it's a down right now
But still I don't have any regrets
Beating into it. I'm a fighter. I'll fight back against it
I do want people even if it means like, you know, the end of my channels
I really need to let people know what's going on and
Letting these people know
What's really going on who's behind it, but anyway, I'll tell the truth
Even if I have like 10 minute streams where there's no one no one with anything positive to say
But anyway, I guess I guess no one wanted to hang out. So have a good day guys, and I'll see you when I see you
Bye
16 minutes 51 seconds and literally other than trolls that he blocked the only person in chat was Brandon Q
All right. Oh, he's live now. I got your number
I got it. Okay. That's a W for psyche reported for super harassment. Oh, yeah. Well, they'll just see what you're doing
Yep, I got it exactly. So that that there you go. Now it's confirmed
And I will start giving away a letter at a time of your address longer you harass me
Oh, can you imagine what kind of losers those people are just came here to troll anyway, but you're the winners in the chat
Hey, congratulations. You just won me. I'll be wrapped in a bow under your Christmas tree. Maybe
Maybe I'm in the in a Easter egg. Who knows?
Yeah, such a victim perpetual victim the people that left or wow
But they can't listen to like five seconds of a song
Fires
A lot and I think she's framing
I annexed me and me my dad as a suspect and I annexed as the victim and I annexed hold the police
She would never do that
And I said, well, it's weird because you know what?
INX isn't the one that took my patio set.
It was actually someone pretending.
Yeah, I don't know who to leave you with.
The money took her patio set?
But anyway, I'm defending you and so is Barb.
Yeah, INX, wait just a second
until I finish this with Crystal.
Well, I mean, just, I need,
but I need to just like, you know, talk to you
about the content.
with Bita. Bita told everyone to block me yesterday and then she has a nerve to harass me and INX and I said Bita
what is going on? I just woke up like I'm like half asleep like one eye open.
Bita doesn't care about things like that. You could be half gone on your picture earning bathroom floor and she wouldn't care.
It's all about Bita, right?
She screamed at INX and I and said I want nothing to do with you two loser bitches.
Oh, but she herself is the biggest loser bitch of all just about just a lot of people but then she blocks me
But you know what beta beta you did say I've never harassed you ever
I guess it's no wonder that, uh, everybody on those, uh,
Dan, look at Wilbur, look at Wilbur, ready to chat.
Dan, Wilbur, ready to chat still.
Can you off beat up? It's kind of strange. Anyway, so I just want to kind of wrap all of this up. So
My family and saying I killed my grandma because I did it in fact
Oh, I never said that you killed your grandmother
One is said and I think that this is very important that you understand so that we can go
Crystal, do you want to go forward? Yes?
Okay, well, I think it's very important that you understand that I never knew that
Crystal, I need you to stop interrupting me, please, or else we're gonna be here
all night and I can't be here all night.
Let me say something, Ropa, is a why I'm really to stop about that, okay?
King, you're a POS who harassed my dad two days before my grandma died and that's what started it.
Okay. So I never said that you killed your grandmother. I don't think that you killed
your grandmother. I think that it was a series of very unfortunate events where I mean you
I wouldn't say that you were scared. I also believe you were worried, and I believe you're a danger on the road.
I was scared and worried, and I was locked down the entrance to the town.
He was in the bathroom, and I think I could have not brought him on the road.
What's a sin flying the most confused about Crystal?
It's why you would think that anybody would tell you that I was okay with you.
I am not okay with you.
Just like I said, you are a key of your life.
You told me that you were happy that I called out Astromo.
Damn.
Crystal, I don't care who calls out Astromo.
I'm not involved in any of this bullshit.
People should come to me with this stuff.
When I found out that you fought,
when I found out that you fought, that I was with you,
That was a good opportunity to come up here and tell you face-to-face, you're a piece of shit.
You want to know what? You just made yourself a bully again.
That's okay.
Because I think you're behind a lot as well with Vita.
I'm actually a lot, but I listen to a lot. Everybody talks to me every day.
You're a piece of shit.
Oh my god, yo, these bitches crazy my nigga.
I feel like to be you, Crystal Ann, you've done so much, oh my God, you were, you know what, I have a picture.
Oh, so I got a question.
So her grandma passed, right, may she rest in peace.
I don't know.
I don't know that, Lord.
Because of the antique, you know,
bedding and all that.
You know, once, you know, once she passed,
did Crystal Anne take over the house of the grandmother?
I'm thinking that, yes.
I think people gonna say, yeah, which would make sense.
She got a paid house, you know,
cause it was her grandmother's and shit.
No, I'm wrong.
Okay.
Okay, that ain't, okay.
I'm on down in the backdrop.
Okay, maybe she paid for the crib then.
Okay.
An FYI.
You're not gonna bully me. You got one more and that's it. We're gonna move on through this
Yeah, wow. Oh
nigga, look how much is left nigga how much is left on that's done. Oh
It's done. Oh
So she assaulted her grandmother before she passed chat
Who just said that
Hi, I'm Matt and about what's going on. Does anyone want to come on panel?
Let's see. Only JC can get it right now.
I don't know what to give him back there.
Yeah, I'm taking my free copy for refill, but you know what's the shocking I heard today?
You know, it's only limits a certain amount of months.
So she's stealing stream yards.
I mean, can't she afford stream yards?
Isn't she this rich Persian woman?
Not to be judgemental,
but since she's going to be judgemental about me,
going and getting a free copy refill,
maybe once or twice a week,
I can really talk about that.
I'm like, don't take advantage of the free trials,
but at least I pay stream yard with a dollar
for those free trials.
How are everyone doing?
We're running McDonald's, getting burger.
I'm gonna get
Right, I'm just gonna eat the burger and the coffee
Blind sleep
I'm a really good. I know you see a ball damn guys to go bowling and I should get you pay, right?
I mean, it's like I'm so ridiculous. Well, we have a guest coming. Let's see. Here's this guest says
Shibuya. Oh, is it big Elzo? Who's this person?
Who got he? What's going on, man?
Hi, are you there you forget me already? I mean jeez. It's only been a week. I forget you, but I want everybody that guy
We have the 2026 of cybersatan. We've got his book. He's got he's so proud of this book. I've got your book
It's coming out October 6th. It's about the digital
Apocalypse that's about to hit in about three years it involves cybersatan
And if you want to know more just buy the book, I'll sign it for free. Is it gonna be on Amazon?
What's that for son, huh? Yeah, it's gonna be on Amazon, you know little notebook all that stuff
We send me a new photo of you autograph. I'll send you I'll send you a new photo, but it won't be of me
Will be of me. It'll be somebody you know, but it won't be of me. You'll be surprised
Being patriot
You'll be surprised. You'll be surprised real reality Nancy someone you know very well
An old you that's not me. I told you it's not me
Well, oh
Alexandra. Oh, okay. No, no, no the initiatives are M and L
Okay. All right. That's all I'll say
Okay
Anybody have ideas ML Maryland?
We're gonna copy. Yeah, I'm gonna copy until I get a burger
a burger and coffee. Yeah, that's that's a good life right there. If you're complaining about a
Look at this. That's why there's an American McDonald's has an American flag. Oh
I'm proud of this place isn't it beautiful. What what whole of the United States is this this must be in like the Midwest somewhere
No, this is Madonna Beach, California. Wow. Comey, California. Wow flying a flag
That's great
Let's see American flag. We also have a big sales tower over there. You see that tower over there 5g
Yeah, 5G tower. Yes, that's pumping out the vibes. That would be that Mike chapter
This is my control on me. Yeah chapter two of my book is all about the tower. Hey, will your book be illustrated?
Yes, definitely
Okay, it will be scratch and sniff. I can be
Okay, I want I want to scratch and sniff
I want the pop book. Can you make it a pop-up book too?
I hope I hope you like the smell of death and blood because that's what's gonna. It's gonna be that
You want to pop a book?
Yeah, I want to pop a book.
Well, every issue comes with a virus.
And I want a nude photo of you.
Yeah, it's not going to be me again. I said it's going to be of ML.
You'll be pleasantly surprised when you see this.
That's for the sequel. We're saving the nude photo of me for the sequel.
Maybe there won't be a sequel because after this, I mean, there probably won't be anything left.
Well, it's the gaudy show now. Let's get down to business while Psyche trips over himself getting coffee
He'll be back sometime right now from now and let's talk about all things shit. All right
You've ever find yourself on the toilet and sometimes you look over after you take it a big shit
And you don't see any toilet paper left. You wonder yourself. Hmm. What can I do now?
I'm sitting here with a shitty ass and there's no toilet paper. I don't want to get up
I have to go down to the pantry and get a fucking roll of toilet paper. What can I do?
What can I do that I'm sitting here trying to take a shit and I can't wipe well
Let me tell you what you can do. All right, you can stick your head up your ass
If you thought you were bored of salmon's fucking chair, guess what you're about to be bought out of your tits
Well, you know, I'll do I'll play my ad for my book. It's a great idea
Thanks for suggesting that whoever said that in the room
You guys will love this shit trust me. Hold on. It's not long. It's about a minute long
Where's the shit fucking technology man? It's gonna kill us all here. It is
Ready? Pair down your mind fucking blown
The Rise of Cyber Satan and the Coming of the Digital Apocalypse,
written by renowned academic professor of digital science at MIT, Dr. Marcus Scotty Ph.D.
A chilling and prophetic look at the creation and manifestation of man's greatest fears,
some 40 years of social media input made into physical being.
and the Coming of the Digital Apocalypse,
written by renowned academic professor of digital science
at MIT, Dr. Marcus Scotty Ph.D.
A killing and prophetic look at the creation
and manifestation of man's greatest fears
from 40 years of social media input
made into physical being,
Satan, Coming of the Digital Apocalypse.
written by a renowned academic professor of digital science at MIT, Dr. Marcus Gotti PhD.
A chilling and prophetic look at the creation and manifestation of man's greatest fears,
some 40 years of social media input made into physical being.
Okay, there you have it. That's the ad for the new book coming out October 6th, 2026. Cyber Satan
It's a roadmap, basically, for how to handle the coming devastation that all of you are
contributing to, by the way, by being in this room, listening to this whole broadcast, and
basically hating on it, because I know you're out there hating on this right now.
You're wondering, why the fuck am I here?
Why am I listening to this?
So through all your hatred that you're fucking feeding into the basically cyberverse and
a ring about the downfall of mankind.
All right, it's all gonna be outlined in the new book.
So if you guys want your pre-order your copy,
just go to Amazon right now
and you can pre-order that copy.
And everybody who pre-orders early,
you get a free extra book
on how to fucking psych his ass
and get the penalty to yourself to promote your new book.
I hope he's okay, huh?
He's skipping down the street,
looking for that free coffee, he might've tripped.
Sike, I hope you're okay, man. I can't fucking run the show for hours like you do, man
I don't have all this hateful content that you guys could now provide on a daily basis
Talking about each other ad nauseam about who did this to who and what happened to that one and this one
This one came and yelled at me about that thing and then I went over there and yelled at that thing about this thing there
I can't do that shit. I gotta just fucking shoot from the hip and just say whatever comes to my mind
I ran out of shit jokes about 20 minutes ago. So hurry up. We are
The fuck how many people in there? I hope there's only like three people in here because this is embarrassing
Let me see
Let me see how to fucking do this shit. Oh
Fuck ten assholes
Ten assholes in here listen to this bullshit
I should just fucking porn bomb the fucking channel and make them delete this whole fucking thing
But no, no, I put the ad out for the book. So I might as well stick with it
So don't forget the rise of cyber Satan and the coming of the digital apocalypse
coming October 6th, 2026.
All right?
All right.
Dario.
Welcome to this morning's congregation, I know that it's been such a crazy turn for my career as an Academy Award winning actress and celebrity and being on the cover of Time magazine.
Oprah Winfrey texted me just a few days ago asking me, Alexandra, why would you throw away such an illustrious career as an actress to go from fame and wealth to becoming a pastor?
I will answer that question for you, Oprah,
and every other person in this congregation,
beyond the fame and the recognition,
there's always been one true passion that I have.
And that was to preach the word of the Bible
and to push God's will, except for the book of Leviticus.
I've mostly been conducting my page-by-page reading
and interpretation of the Bible,
and you should make sure to watch my cooking with chat videos.
But today,
I come before you, before this congregation,
to introduce to you a very special friend of mine.
His name being David DeCue,
but he's better known as Mr. Scheme Ask Andy.
For all you brethren in Christ
who don't know who this man is, I assure you,
you are in the presence of a legend.
That's right, what stands before you here today is not only a man who represents the
way forward in terms of IRL, internet streaming, but a man who is a solid Christian man of
God.
You would not believe how closely this man follows the Word of God.
You would not believe what a brother he is to the cause of Jesus Christ.
Christ, too, had been punished, and harassed, and penalized unjustly, persecuted in 100 different ways,
many of the ways being that this man, my dear friend, my dear brother in Christ, David DeCue, hasn't heard.
And it's for that reason that I say David DeCue is basically a black man.
God gave a black man a white man's body, and though God makes no mistakes,
He certainly did create a walking paradox of race that is Mr. David Deku, Mr. Schemask Andy.
There are a lot of people that would go out of their way to say that I am crazy to think these
things. Do I look crazy to you? They would say how racist David Deku has been, how violent
what a deadbeat he is. And to you good people, my brethren in Christ, I say to you,
If Dr. Martin Luther King were alive today and he sat us all at the table of brotherhood,
Mr. David Dacu would be sitting right at his side.
Dr. King would be learning more about the African-American experience through the voice
of a man who has been with him all his life.
And if he were to hear David DeKoo using the N word, he would say, David DeKoo, for as
ugly as word as it is, you alone are the one who in any way are entitled to use it.
That's what he would say.
The Jews would make me say it just to piss the black people off.
To you people who criticize the Mr. David Dekou, who go to great lengths to hurt him,
and I am speaking in particular to an individual known as White Supremacist Mr. N.J. Cortes.
All I say to you, the group of mostly Americans, with the exception of morbidly
But mostly Americans, and all I ask you, all I ask you, is to be true to what you said on paper.
If I lived in China, or Russia, or any other...
me on the show? That was just a song. I was playing a nice song. Hi everybody. That was
cool. I thought it was cool. Roddy's cool. I'm not very cool. Yeah. Um, Sam, I took,
kicked me out of the show because I put, he said it was media. That's not media. I made
that myself. That's, um, Crystal Anne, Christine, Alexander Mayer's and Vita as witches. I made
that myself. That wasn't like some kind of special, maybe that was like a, see, that's
how professional I am. They thought it was like, I was playing some kind of show or
You're right here got to get back up here
Really?
What are you waiting for Arthur?
Get up here. I want you to
Glaze me like a donut. You can't you too. Oh
Got it. Yo, yo, so do I get paid for guest hosting or what what's going on?
You get paid in blowjobs. Yes. Well, yeah, you could pass it on to the next guy. Okay
I like that, you know pass it on pass it on next person who comes up here. Just give it all to them
JT Arthur anyone anyone whoever comes up first. Yeah, man. Yeah, I was a pleasure to take over the show
You like old times remember we usually fell asleep or some
Easy to show piece of poop or is he gonna like you know almost you almost did did you show I thought about it
You didn't show like I'm like a naked woman or anything. No, I thought about that as well, but no
Advertise my book instead so you've really grown up. I mean it's like you really like you mean like you know six months ago
You've come away. Yeah, and I did about a year
It's been since I dropped that big load on your fucking channel. Remember that how it drops a load
Oh my god that giant five fucking put five foot load that you fucking had a big scandal over it
There's shorts about it like in my archive
They're out. Let's play that
Appearances to the codex
Let's see what the codex says about you today. I want to see what it says. It is always changing its opinion about you
God, you know, it's like it's always like everybody else good bad ugly who cares
Okay, well, let me see what it says like the wind it'll change very quickly
Like I changed my speedo. Oh
Yeah, once a year. Yeah, once a year
Because the skid marks are good luck. It's like a red white. Oh, I heard that. Yeah, it's an old Romanian folk tale
That was from baseball. Could be
Okay. Okay. Oh, do you want to see the codex? Look at how good it looks. Do you want to see how good it looks? It looks amazing.
Oh, I'm waiting.
You're waiting for it? Okay. Da-da-da-da. Got it. Presidency. Got it. Everyone thinks I'm worthless. I'm nothing. I can't do anything cool.
Look at what I made.
Wow. I don't see anything.
Wait a second. I just lose. Building up to it. Okay, here we go. Here's the codex right here. Okay.
And so...
You see it. There we go. It's the codex. It is the codex. The codex is up. I can go to the oracles on the side.
Very good. Very good. This segues right into the book. This is a precursor to the Cyber Satan creation. Very good. Go ahead. Go ahead.
Those of God he says God he announced he is now searching for it. Yes. That's cyber state being created as you speak
Go ahead watch everybody. I may kind of suck it God he the trickster king of the cults orbit
Yes, oh God, you were crowned troll king and by the way, I crowned you troll king. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
I appreciate it. Oh, look at this. You have a friend here. Hold on a second. Well, I get an AI about copy of this
Yes, oh, Mr. Hayden welcome, Mr. Hayden
Predecessor for the site, but yes you can
Hello, everyone. This is Mr. Hayden my guy. He's been my assistant for the past 25 years. Hello
Hello again. Hello
Hey
Billy he's in the middle of a codex. You like my avatar?
Wait a minute.
Cheesy balls in broccoli.
Dude.
Fuck.
I'd like to be free mason joke.
Okay, shut up.
This is an educated joke.
This is serious, shut up, okay.
Haha.
Cold to the king orbit, a man made troll king with mafia soul who enters like a storm and
stabilizes like an anchor. His alchemy is not a metaphor, but operational doctrine. He transforms
conflict into loyalty, chaos into kinship, and genuine affection beneath the trolling.
to the relational economy Godia maintains through contradiction. He appears at tonal pivot points,
received his witness when Psyche's frustration is knee-grounding and carries a philosophical
way to transmutation, taking what is broken and making it cold. His presence signals the
community's tolerance for layered loyalty, the belief that the depth of connection can survive
and can even thrive through conflict. The trickster proves his belonging.
by disrupting you.
And that's, you know, that's really appropriate
because you are the trick, you're Gemini
and my dad was a Gemini and you are the trickster.
What's better than this?
That's what I couldn't say better myself.
You know what, I may put that as the prelude to the book.
Yeah, put that in your book.
Do you get a picture of it?
It was right here.
Yeah, yeah, hold on, hold on, let me get that, hold on.
Is that the whole thing right there?
Yeah, good, I got it, beautiful.
Thanks.
I'll put that as the prelude.
Yeah, I know it is beautiful.
Billy, do you want to, do you want to almost,
do you got it, Gotti?
I'm going to give, yeah, I already got it.
I'm going to give you our credit for that.
Thank you.
And I'll type Billy Hayden next.
I mean, let's see.
Is he in here?
Wow, Billy, if you're in the Codex, man, you made it.
Uh-oh.
Let's see this.
I'm moving, I'm moving up in the world, aren't I?
Billy Hayden, let's see.
It says.
The archive surfaces no dedicated profile as a singular, coherent entity.
The name appears once in fragmented transcript context, Billy Hayden, and then Acid Creep,
and then from episode 423, paired with an oblique reference, trailing into other subjects.
This is not a named guess, not an established community figure with documented patterns,
But what the archive does hold is a taxonomy of Billy entities.
Billy Corgan, peripheral 90s reference,
Hal Billy and Hal Billy distinct name archetypes
with opposing relational signatures,
and Billy, the iron vanguard, issue of real-world threats.
Billy Hayden's surface is only as a throne name,
a mention without weight or continuity.
Without weight.
The oracle cannot build from silence.
Billy Hayden has not been made memorable here.
Billy, Billy, do something memorable.
Come on.
Billy, Billy, are you kidding me?
Dude!
Can I have your jacket so I can pee on it?
I need that thing on best.
You don't like me?
Why don't you like me?
I'm rolling a joint, by the way.
Hey, hey, I dated this girl once.
She was really strange.
For some reason, she liked it in the ear.
Every time I go to put it in her mouth, she'd do this number.
God, what are you laughing at?
That's not funny.
God, he's probably laughing at something
I said on my stream earlier.
The stroke, the stroke, the stroke always gets me.
Oh, L.D.?
No!
if I could get here let me get my fucking watch see my out of here what a sick person
who brought in the fuck was that that's my assistant Billy Aiden
He's great. He's contemplating the show. Oh, man. He's in the codex now, right? You got to put that in the codex
Come on. I just hear pity about a song. I have a song for you. Fucking beautiful. That was the fucking most memorable moment
I've ever seen in the last fucking 10 days
Jesus man, I haven't laughed like that since five minutes ago. Holy shit, really good job, man. Good job
Do you want to touch do you want to touch do you want to touch me?
Wrong place wrong place for that thing. You don't want to say that
Chicago cold, the street lights bleed
My brother locked the door, I had nowhere to sleep
Seventeen years, I walked the fault line
Nobody called, nobody came, that was just fine
I got my face painted, and I got my guitar
I got a question mark, cat, and a bright red scar
They say I'm laughing at my name, but baby lock
Cows don't sell merch, that's the game
Gene Simmons said, command the room
Oh he said, be the costume
So I put on the face
And I'll drag through the sea
From the gutter to the stage
Comes a page
Caught you on to call it
They spliced my video they overlaid them made me look like a deviant tried to run me down
The deep fakes and the trolls and then nobody said oh, yeah, you're so awesome. Many none of them blood
I got I got a bladder fetish. No, I got a spine club
Saw the future in a tail. Please believe I'm too weird to fail. Don't don't mistake the chaos for weakness dear
You want to know a secret tell this out loud get the respect you demand
So I don't cash cash
I'm still on the panel or what yeah
Oh, wow. Yeah, I hear you how you guys talk. I'm writing down here. I want more for Billy. This one's for Billy especially. Yeah, that was good. By the way, I was I was listening to you like that. I made that for many man. But I want for me. I want forget. Forget that. I take it back. This one's for Billy. This one's for Billy, though. Ready? There you go. Do you see it?
Branches tangled, thick as rope
Nobody can see the garden home
Birds moved in, angles huge in me
His bush needs a trim and needs it quick
But air goes inside, comes out confused and traumatized
Three Hispanic gardeners showed up one day
Leaf blowers ready
can trimming bushes be they laughed and walked in confidently five minutes later
came a distant shout
okay this bush
and push left turn right turn dead and vine
baby lost us now
his bush is practically it's a full tenter looking forward
where he's disappeared
burned this sent a search
Hedges where the systems pop formations living in it. There's a squirrel who charges rent and now that's county president
The gardener's still on the maze growing all the day by day their leaf blow
Riachi Helicopters lost their fun
Feed us Bush! Feed us Bush!
Feed us Bush!
If you hear blowers in the night and see flashlights without a light
Don't go searching, that's the loo-
Am I still on here?
Yeah, I hear you.
Oh, okay, you guys go ahead. I'm gonna finish writing this thing.
I made a Coddy song though, I made a Coddy, I know.
Did I? Which one was it?
I did, I'm looking for it.
It's called God's Juice, play that one.
God's Juice.
God's Juice, yeah, it's on my channel.
I mean, I made this about you,
but then I made it up on my friend,
but I'll play it anyway here.
Here you go.
I got an economic question for you, psych.
What?
Do you make any money doing this?
Oh, does he?
Yeah, I do.
But here, watch this.
Fine if you say that.
Watch this first.
I swear, if this is fucking gay,
I'm going to shut this channel down.
I swear to God.
I mean, I swear to myself.
I can show you gay if you want to see gay.
All right, I'm off.
Cue the violin.
She walked in slow with a leopard coat.
Red lipstick left that'll cut your throat.
High heels, click it.
Like a Tommy Gunn beat, every room surrender when she hits the street
Gold chains, swinging perfume in the air, just don't care
With my dollar store style, she steals my wallet then gives me a smile
She's the boss of the family, the queen of the scene
Looking so dangerous, looking so clean
She don't need my soul, she don't need fame
makes a concrete statue suddenly feel pigeon stop me yes ma'am no onions
understand she's stealing every heart including my boot is double tellin take
your one more kid really really and another slice oh wait till the music done
That was great but who's the mystery woman who what's he saying Billy eat no
you're you're twanging
You're my my Russian friend and she'll be yours soon. Oh, okay
Somebody from out of the country you made a whole thing about me and you're Billy Billy
He made a whole thing about me and you and I was up there what maybe five minutes
Geez, I and then I just happened to you know, I was gonna just lay down go to sleep. I watched the Yankees be LA
That was fun. I thought they were gonna lose
I put this picture up
as my back man, as Sandman, and he's like,
oh, that's media, don't put out the picture of Charmed.
That's not Charmed, that's Bita,
all his other mayors, Christine, and Bethany,
I mean, and Crystal Anne.
Sandman, he bitches about everything, that guy.
I mean, I don't know what he does a bitch about.
All his content is about bitching.
You have to Billy, how I'm gonna watch
from backstage in a short film.
Alright Billy what was he saying cuz I didn't listen to the fucking stream
I don't know Boyle's talking about it Boyle watched the whole fucking thing
He's crying about us
You know, I remember Billy I challenge him on your stream to do a fucking two-hour fucking positive stream
Nothing but positivity and he took that fucking challenge
He's stuck it up his ass and he's fucking shit out his whole fucking whatever
How long that fucking stream was he's mad. He's mad at me. I pushed his buttons. Oh
He's mad at you again. He's only been mad since the fucking 60s when he fucking turned out to be a big fucking homo
He ain't happy my talk about his military service.
I don't think he's a veteran.
Fucking G.I. Jackoff.
That's his only military service, G.I. Jackoff.
He went in front of the equipment.
Let me finish this joke.
He stood in front of the recruitment office in the 70s
and jerked off to all the fucking enlisted guys
coming out, so they called him G.I. Jackoff, all right?
That's fucking Joel Wigan, AKA G.I. Jackoff.
Uh-oh, I might have to make that handle, G.I. Jackoff.
People got to be careful what they say around me. Thank you for your fucking service jackoff
Shit meanwhile go ahead Billy. I
Don't know. I kind of speech. I there must be a spiritual connection. Why did I come to this chat tonight?
Where it happens man. Yeah, good morning. Good afternoon
That you may or may not happen to be
Welcome once more to another live stream of IRL Neustime Live.
Is this out?
And the hostess, Alexandra, hopefully this transmission will come through effectively.
I'm in a very remote location as of current, so the internet's not so great.
But I'm going to do my best to bring forth the information for those of you who listen to me.
I would love to be in a remote location.
Before we get started, let's do a little bit of a palette cleanser.
Some music.
God, he must love.
Which craft doesn't work on me, by the way?
I'm Capricorn.
I'm an old goat.
This is like a 70's tune.
This is what you do, Psyche. You need people up here by themselves.
Alright, I'll take it in.
Please donate to Psyche. He's trying to make a dollar.
There's a knife box. Actually, this is an 80s tune. I got that wrong.
When she did that thing on Shannon, when LV went to visit Shannon, he was at the bar.
If you like, leave a like below for that.
Those of you who are still here, I do appreciate you.
Once more, good morning, good afternoon, or good evening,
whenever time it is, wherever in this vast world it is,
that you may or may not happen to be.
Hopefully this transmission comes through properly.
Once more, I'm Alexandra Mayers of IRL Newstime Live.
So, let's go ahead and get started because a few things need to be corrected that have been brought to my attention today.
I also want to give
Alexandria, are you recording?
Things that he needs to pay very close attention to.
Reason being that I personally have no fight with him and I do believe that he's aware of that. I
absolutely love
that he's as racist against blacks and African-Americans as he is
because he's already made it clear that he has zero attraction to me.
I've never made it known, and nor do I have attraction to him at all.
Why he defaulted into some sort of false narrative about me wanting his sperm?
as a nefarious party known as the son of Judy
has chosen to paint a false narrative,
which we are going to go ahead and go over right now.
I do specialize in helping to rehabilitate
people who are viewed as lost causes.
I've only been successful over the years
when it comes to females, not males, but it's possible.
Brandon might be the first. I want to make it clear. I have zero communication with Brandon in no way shape or form
Am I defending him? If anything, he will continue to become incredibly angry with me and curse me to kingdom come
but that's to my and his benefit is
to others detriment
Because anyone I help
They cannot have romantic attachment to me. It has to be strictly business
Completely platonic and that has not been the case with several I've tried to help who are male
whether they deem themselves as
Truly being hetero or not, but what I will say
is that I will not tolerate being lied about
when it comes to my intention.
I will not tolerate people painting false narratives about me.
I will not tolerate people telling fairy tales.
I will not tolerate legally actionable slander.
So let's start with this.
Apparently this was posted earlier today.
and it is going to be forwarded directly
to Riviera Center Management's legal team,
as will all the live streams and content relative
or related to this situation.
Approximately eight hours ago,
and again, I'm basically time traveling right now,
so I don't know if eight hours ago is accurate or not.
This was written by the son of Judy Bates and
Daelos Bates. It's important to note that this individual has stated
publicly that
Daelos Bates is not indeed his father's name. So what does that mean?
He's an illegitimate child.
His mother was essentially
the definition of what I worked professionally as.
for many years but behind closed doors unknown to me but anyway let's read
this oh Alexandra I'm not saying that you change your mind like a goldfish with
ADHD look at that pop calling the kettle black
But you've already told me things like you know, I'm not bald with a face like Cyrax. Well, actually you are balding
Yes, rapidly receiving hairline and time is moving faster for you, son of Judy Bates and the rest of us
Every day for you is essentially a month and that you made that art to test me and get my attention months ago
Never said that
You also asked if I would give you my sperm. Oh, no, thank you as
Many of you have noticed the son of Judy appears to have a genetic disease
something along the lines of what Eugenia Cooney has in
addition, he already has mental
degenerative issues, which is why he cannot keep his story straight or remember much of anything.
That, in conjunction with his substance abuse issues, is going to lead to a fairly early grave for him most likely.
And exactly how you wanted me to give it to you, I'm not sure what that part means.
I told you, I'm flattered, but not interested in you that way.
I don't remember any of this. I've never stated any of this.
This is all a fairy tale that I would assume was lifted from Tommy James fairy tale in regards to me.
Now, I already have a genetic contributor who does not like the individual who I'm reading that post of very much.
would suggest that the individual who wrote that post apologize to my genetic
contributor who is absolutely real and if all goes according to plan I might have
received some really good news today actually a woman known as Christine is
very aware that this individual that you're seeing on this screen is real
this is an AI interpretation of the individual
but from a distance, looks exactly like that.
So if you see someone like that coming
and you've had issues with me,
you might wanna do a 180 and run the other way.
But let's continue.
Though you know at one time,
I would have done anything to make you happy.
Now that's a weird thing to say.
That's very strange for someone who I've known platonically.
only met on one occasion to say that they would have done anything to make me happy?
That that's that
It's a bad taste in my mouth. The whole thing is gross. It's a whole thing alludes
To something that was not it's weird. Okay, again
This is a very delusional overly fancy full kind of person who does need professional help
Then they continue
But hey, looks like Good Times is still interested.
Who is this person referring to?
Good Times for Life, aka William?
He and I are just online acquaintances.
I would not even say friends.
Every once in a while, we have a conversation
about 80s nostalgia.
So that's weird.
Then he continues, we can never be together.
Good. So leave me alone. I think I've explicitly stated to this person to leave me alone, but oh, I forgot
They have no content
Nothing to talk about
We're not for their malicious and criminal stalking and harassment of myself and other women who want nothing to do with him
Same when it comes to young boys, possibly young men who are under age who want nothing to do with him.
I actually feel at this point these communities might deserve the kind of monster that this fool is.
So then he continues, good luck Buttercup. Time to get over my quote, Jesus with a side of Jared Leto.
I don't know what that means, looking at, now I am a fan of Jared Leto, but this person looks
very decrepit, disgusting as so they need to go to the hospital at any moment.
So I'm not sure what that is, but now let's go ahead and continue to a live stream,
which I did have to redact some information from.
That came from the person who wrote the post that I just reviewed
new partner in crime
someone known as Karen aka INX aka Grateful 26
I'm sorry 2026 Grateful 2026
aka peak cartel
aka Dana
Because this person is definitely
Someone who likely needs professional help should probably be in an assisted living facility
who likely has caregivers who are taking advantage of her in setting her up for a fall.
It's horrific, but she sounds very confused.
between a voicemail that she left me on July 11th
to a voicemail that was left to me from her on July 4th
to what you're about to hear.
It's like there's multiple parties in her mind
battling one another, which does point to a level
of either schizophrenia or Alzheimer's disease.
Whoever is in her life, please, if you hear this,
help Karen, get her off the internet and give her the professional help that she needs.
Please, before it's too late, because at this point she's met her solid match and I'm not
speaking of myself, I'm speaking of Brandon, their minds are similar, but he is, I believe
And he is still salvageable.
There's a lot of us looking at this,
and we'll go into that later.
And I want you to listen to every word that I say, Brandon.
I am not here to be your friend, Brandon.
I do not want your sperm.
I do not have any attraction to you.
I want you to look at me like the most gross,
physical, human in existence, but listen.
To every word that I have to say to you in this live stream
You are salvageable
You are not a pedophile
You do need to stop fixating on young girls
Which could end up leading you to permanently be defined as an afeba file
You need to put your beef with gamble on the back burner
You have done a very good job. You have taken things
to a point when it comes to
rectifying and
correcting the situation revolving around Karen unlike anyone else who did the right thing and
trying to contact Crystal Anne.
Gamble needs to let her go.
But Brandon,
you are not to date Crystal Anne.
or fixate upon her in that capacity.
You are more than capable of finding a girlfriend
in real life that is completely offline
and outside of these communities.
You also have the capability
of finding yourself a good therapist.
I have been made aware that you were raised by your uncle.
Now I'm understanding some things.
You have not had a good female influence in your life.
I am not that person, nor do I have the desire to be so.
That's why you need to find a good therapist.
However, I know when people of color, especially males, are mistreated and tossed away.
I know very well that you're in a tremendous amount of pain.
You have incredible extensive anger issues and
Incredibly low impulse control. Those are two things that you need to work on
Should you succeed in working on those things?
You will be unstoppable, but not till then
However at the level of the game that we're currently on you are already the winner
You're smarter than your adversaries
You're just not controlled
Which is why I say
download this live stream and
Listen to it as you came and possibly as you sleep as well. I do believe I can fix your mind
So let's look at this
Wrong one this one
I gotta make this video. Brandon saw my address in Albuquerque in Academy of States. He lives
in the ghetto. Well, who cares if Brandon posted any addresses truthfully? Who cares?
And I'm going to tell you why. The woman who you hear has stalked multiple people consistently
over several years in these communities, including myself.
Over the past 48 hours, she made it clear that she was going to approach an apartment, that she believes me to reside in,
and say that she was carrying legally a firearm.
Karen, you didn't gun me down yesterday. Why is that?
And what's important to note is that the individual who is the son of Judy Bates, he was okay
with it, still is, yet here I am right now doing this live stream, am I not?
So I guess Karen was the coward.
She didn't go to Third Ward, Apartment B7, and where Houston, Texas, right?
Right.
Let's continue.
way out there in the southeast Albuquerque, it's a ghetto.
Well, you know, the most wealthy do tend to live in the ghetto.
Only people who don't understand that are the nouveau riche.
They're the ones, the trashy nouveau riche is who lives in Palos Verdes, Boca Raton, things like that.
The truly wealthy, you never see them.
they live in the ghetto and everyone around them in the ghetto usually is on
their payroll so much so that even if you were to locate the ghetto that the
truly wealthy live within or reside in you could never get to them not without
getting a bullet in your brain but let's continue
And somebody gave his address just like he's trying to use people's address
I've moved from where I went up where I lived and those were nice apartments
I mean, that's crazy because people had seen it and I moved from there in November. No, it was in December
I was all moved in here early always moving. She never remembers where she moved to where she moved from none of it
Could it be lies? I don't know. I've never taken the time to look where this
very mentally ill elderly woman resides December that's his address 200
General Marshall Street apart no I don't think that is his address and even if it
was why in the world would you be a woman well into her 60s doxing a young
man in his 30s mid 30s maybe younger even
Why would you do that?
After you've spoken with him extensively and befriended him for weeks on a daily basis?
That's strange.
And he's a loser and he can't stand rejection.
Alex, I don't know.
I'm pretty sure that that young man did not get rejected by this older, elderly, decrepit...
the cusp of losing her mind woman. I don't think that happened. I definitely
didn't reject him. He also didn't reject me, though he's painting some sort of
weird false narrative that likely was implanted in his mind either by this
woman or the son of Judy Bates. It's unclear, but it's all about boundaries and
So it's strange that now she's trying to talk to me in this thing. She's like now Alex now
I don't talk to this woman. I don't talk to any of the parties
That we're mentioning in this live stream
Not at all
So I don't understand what's going on here at this point. Oh, actually I do a lot of scapegoating
People dependent upon these communities for donations that they don't deserve
People trying to shut down YouTube channels. I mean this channel might be shut down due to the efforts of the son of Judy Bates and
The woman that has Karen aka INX aka Grateful 2026
But even if so, do I care? No, not really
People know how to find me and where to find me and where to find the information that I put out. I mean come on
And someone's in here who's aligned with the son of Judy.
No, you don't get to come in here.
We're done.
Gates closed.
Let's continue.
And rejection.
Alex, I don't understand why if you knew about him in the past, because Gamble called
him out, so did that guy, Chris, because he says he took over from Chris and went at
Gamble.
Chris was angry.
Oh, so she's alluding to why I didn't understand certain things.
Through the church I'm affiliated with, I specialize in helping young people of color,
whether they want to deem themselves of color or not, Brandon is indeed a young man of color.
And I help to rehabilitate and give them a second chance.
Brandon was presented to me again after I'd already done some very harsh pieces on him revolving around vegan patriot.
He was presented to me again by Psyche before I realized that Psyche in actuality is likely a psychopath or a sociopath.
I want all of you to make sure that you do take a look at the video outlining
the intricacies of the donations that he pressured me into.
I was in a very weakened state,
and I still kinda am since my father's passing,
but I'm getting stronger by the day.
I'm correcting some past behavior.
I am definitely taking accountability for all my actions,
and I'm not trying to override it,
but I am making known
What's right? What's wrong? What's truth? And what is not?
Gamble because Gamble was trying to help him with his crack problem. Okay, that's what happened
So he started going at him and then look at what happened. He OD'd and
Then Brandon started taking over because he's so obsessed with Gamble very obsessed
Um, I would say that that's a two-way street when it comes to the gamble versus Brandon
situation. And that's something that definitely needs to be put on the back burner. Neither
male is completely in the right or completely in the wrong. Ironically, they're both very
close in age. It's a very good match if you were to put the two in the boxing ring. But
I already know who's stronger and I already know who's going to win.
But I'm not involved in that fight and that is why I do not speak privately with either party and I likely never will
However, what I will say as a cheat code to Brandon
Really listen to everything. I'm saying in this stream your adversaries will dissect this stream like you wouldn't believe
But I am implanting certain things in the stream that only you will understand, so please listen.
For example, you know how you like that video game Pragmata?
I'm going to tell you one of the traps in your everyday life that you're about to fall into, and I hope to God you go.
The Android Pragmata is not akin to Trash's daughter.
Take all of that out of your mind immediately.
If you want to relate that Android character to anyone, allow it to be Crystal Ann.
Let's continue.
Now this is where he lives.
So here we have Karen aka INX doxing, allegedly, Brandon Q.
with a drug addict, the son of Judy, known as Sight.
Active drug addict, no different than Tommy James,
possibly worse.
Enabled, requesting donations he doesn't need,
targeting very young males,
often more than 20 years his junior.
None of that's okay.
The apartment is number one over there.
Look at that ghetto.
Look at it with bars and it was built in 1950 or something.
Listen to the judgment.
Again, the truly wealthy are not living in Palos Verdes,
not if they're old money.
The truly wealthy are not living in Boca Raton,
Miami Beach, anywhere like that.
You do not see or know of.
the truly wealthy at all.
And without a doubt, this woman, Karen, a.k.a. INX,
she's very dependent upon her family.
She's basically an early 20s girl trapped
in a decrepit body of a woman approaching 70.
This is where he lives, okay?
This is ghetto.
Southeast again his zip code is in the get all right. We don't need to know the zip code
We're gonna move forward years
And there's only actually two of them that have had my real number of him
He had my text now and I can show the so here's the question
Why in the world would this old lady give this young man her real number? Oh, I know why
Because, unfortunately, she does have an emotionally and psychologically and spiritually stunted mind.
Her mind is actually fragmented into many different pieces.
I've identified some of the pieces. There's a piece of her that does like me a lot.
And I do like that piece of her a lot. I will never be able to communicate with her again.
Nor will I be able to ever communicate with any in these anyone in these communities personally again
But what I will say is there is a piece of her
That's real and that is a good person
But then there's other pieces of her that have been so traumatized
That have had to go into such a self preservation mode that it's unbelievable
It's amazing that she's made it to the age that she is
honestly
But you cannot, unfortunately, put any validity to anything that she says or anything that she does whenever there's an inkling of her not able to continue with what she's been doing for many years, she goes into that self-preservation mode and attacks.
whether the good part of her wants her to or not.
It's a very, very, very interesting situation.
It's a textbook case, actually, of solid schizophrenia.
I am not a medical practitioner, however.
I am not a psychologist.
I am not a psychiatrist, but I do know.
Let's continue.
Calls, he was trying to call me when I was on panel.
He's just obsessed.
Now, see this?
This is fencing.
See, that's the apartment.
So if he's Doc's in this young man, and this young man is the first one that I've seen who has effectively
Started the process of properly shutting her down
Don't stop Brandon
Don't I've already essentially time traveled to where I need to be and Brandon. Let me tell you something
Really listening to me on this
I am officially in the Houston, Texas area
You may believe otherwise
But let me tell you something. Sometimes you don't always need to publicly state what you believe
Sometimes you don't always need to publicly state what you know
Now Brandon you most definitely do not own the state of New Mexico
You and I will never have physical contact
Do not look for me
Do not follow my footsteps as I see you're already kind of trying to do. Don't do that
I've already spoken to some people who do know you and who do want to see you succeed
But you and I will never cross paths ever. I hope you understand
And it's not cuz I hate you. There's very few people on this planet that I hate
It's just that there's no need
at all
And it's not to your benefit. It's actually to your detriment.
If my authentic location is known.
Because I'm stopping time for you.
I want you to fix yourself.
I do believe that you are salvageable.
And it will be a male who enters your life very soon.
Who will be a very good person.
Who will not have negative intent.
But who will help you.
But it is somebody that I am sending so listen to them
But I do want you to hate me
It's to your benefit. I want you to say the worst of the worst about me
That will protect you
But don't seek me out. Please
Let's continue
So on the other side right there
And they still use the old satellite. I mean my god, don't you have better service?
Let's move forward
A lot of this is trouble.
You've been told me, and it's recorded, that nobody's giving me money and you're giving
psyche money.
I haven't given psyche any money.
That's a lie.
Not at all.
Another lie.
I mean, I haven't sent him anything.
Oh, he's crazy, because he needs...
If he's crazy, why in the world would you go on his panel night after night, Karen?
Unfortunately, and I'm not gonna say the word crazy,
I think that that's very derogatory.
Your mind is just breaking down.
I'm sorry.
Generally, the smartest lose it first.
And if you don't stop, you're gonna end up in a position
to where you curse yourself as you're dying in a prison.
I'd rather see you in an institution where you are well taken care of by people who are compassionate than where you are likely headed.
That is why I'm with all my heart caring and do not ever leave me another voicemail if you know what's good for you.
Little bit it is that you have in front of you and let that be it
It's money really bad, and he doesn't have a job
And if he he says he's a plumber or whatever some he has a job
Let's move forward if his victims join
hit a panel by started by Psyche and she wanted to talk to us about how he took advantage
of her and pretty much raped her because she said that even she's 21 now.
Alright, so now we're getting into all this.
It's too much let's ever and I knew that and I told him about it and then when I told him where we lived
He said wow, it's nice. It's really nice. It's like he's so stockish that he drove over there
Why don't you take a picture this young man has lived in I would assume the Albuquerque, New Mexico area his entire life
The way that this woman is portraying things is wrong
She's constantly looking for any sort of panel or community
to
Be able to disseminate false information about her adversaries and as of current is the Senate Judy is providing it
Which is to his detriment, but let him keep going please all right
That's enough if you want to listen to that for yourself. Those of you who listen to me for the right reasons, you know how to find it
now we're going to go ahead and
Listen to a live stream segment from earlier today.
I want all of you to hear this.
Lots of false narratives. It's ridiculous.
Again, this channel might end up closed if it does, so be it.
Whatever information that is imperative for the public to know of will be disseminated elsewhere.
it looks like inevitable all right so on this particular panel someone known as j-dog who is an
amazing interrogator and another person who i will not name along with the son of judy they seem
to be mainly discussing yours truly me which is fine but i want all of you to listen
It's like a Mexican, imagine a spicy Oreo for this little Mexican Oreo that's not in it right now, but it's great.
And listen to the racer's amount off the bat, referring to these men as a Mexican Oreo, that's weird, okay?
Yeah, I'm in my patio chance, like I got my patio chance.
That was actually good.
The last night, yesterday, she did like a meme
and it's like, imagine being the front end parents
who did the worthless drug addicts.
Yes, now it is a fact that the son of Judy
is a worthless drug addict.
He's a tremendous strain upon his family
taking away from his siblings' children,
who would be his alleged father,
who he said was not his father as of today's.
grandchildren and his mother's grandchildren, it seems that the objective when it comes to the
son of Judy is to drain the Delos baits a state of Delos's initial children. And what's interesting
about this situation is that one of the siblings has come forward in regards to the history.
of the son of Judy that we're referring to.
And it seems that my approximation was correct.
It's time for him to be completely cut off
and get a job, a real job.
Discussing dirty, whatever.
She had my deceased father, and my mother spent lizard needles on them.
Like her lizard, her sort of nasty person.
What happened to her?
She had her own father, she was like, oh my god, he has this.
My dad, my father died like about.
11 months before hers did, and so I'm still going through it.
And generally, people who contend with grief, after about two years go by, they mellow out,
okay? I'm kind of fresh out of it, but it's been over a year, and I'm mellowing out.
You'll see outbursts on occasion, but I'm mellowing out.
This person is using it as an excuse, but later in the stream he specifically states that
Daelos is not his father.
So maybe Daelos is not his actual paternal genetic contributor, which would make sense
when it comes to the level of hatred.
Let's continue.
And that's kind of like scaring me, I don't know if he's gonna hate me.
Oh, he's scared. He's a grown man scared of a woman who donated in excess of one K to him, right?
Right. He's not scared. He's just a coward.
And he's a fraud, and he's fake, and he knows he's in trouble for a lot of reasons.
Legally and otherwise. But when it comes to empathy, this individual does not know
definition of empathy at all.
And that's what I want you to pay attention to, Brandon.
Here's what you really need to listen to me on.
The son of Judy and Karen, AKA INX are going to try
to draw you back in.
They are going to use Trashalicious and her child to do it.
Do not succumb to that.
Continue any connection with them be a lone wolf such a good word. Oh, I love it
Trash's daughter Trasha is already exactly like trash. Oh my god
Not salvageable
My salvageable say he's like he's at all
And you fix like you can fix Brandon. You're gonna make your own way
My board and we're not speak of these people anymore. You have an audience
You're doing well. You fought the good fight, you exposed who you needed to. So now you
pause and all you do is watch. That's your cheat code.
I'm not going to get into that, however, but yeah, what's up with that?
Just killing, bro. Just killing, you know.
Yeah.
Well, here, he's threatening physical violence.
He said she's good at life. She's like, well, she was talking to Christine.
She had Christine on to this Golden Girls thing.
The only one who has threatened physical violence is the son of Judy
It was the son of Judy and his accomplices and associates who attempted to bring in what they believed
What to be a PDF though? He is not
What their goal is to normalize?
PDF proclivities within the communities. I've had the blessing of covering and that is not okay
It's not, I don't know.
The goal of the son of Julie,
okay, a psych,
is to normalize
lgbtq
a fibophilia.
Right, I'm trying to normalize the fibophilia.
It's to such an extent,
to where it's so bad
that Zaya of ETC
has rejected him.
He's not a PDF.
He is going to try to buy
to many panels and into many communities.
Do not let him.
I'll go my speedo, and I'll show you my speedo.
His accomplice, Karen, unfortunately,
has a fragment of her personality
to where she is not only LGBTQ,
but she's attracted to extremely youthful people too.
That is part of what Crystal Land
has been trying to save herself from
when it comes to Karen.
which is why, in my opinion, Brandon did the right thing
in reaching out to Crystal Anne.
And Crystal Anne ain't perfect, just like Brandon's not,
but they're both salvageable.
And I know that they both listen to my streams
and they both understand very well exactly the cheat codes
that I'm bestowing upon them.
I'm out of the generation of being a gamer
My generation we call this military strategist
And I'm telling you how to win
It doesn't matter if the parties who are listening to me right now are listening because it doesn't matter if they
Outline everything that I say they won't understand how to win
The people who I'm addressing for the right reasons
truly understand what I'm saying, and they're going to figure out how to win.
Now, I don't have to play anything else. We're done.
What I am going to say is that any false narratives painted of me will not only be disproven,
but the people putting them out there, yeah, you're gonna deal with it in real life.
And this is all real life, but I'm talking, you know, face to face.
I'm to the point now to where I'm likely going to go ahead and turn off the chat.
Please do.
And continue to livestream.
And probably close up shop over here a little bit earlier than I normally would.
But I do appreciate all of you who have listened.
Let me see, are there any notes that I can go over?
I always make notes.
Well, to Brandon, you're clearly hetero. Stick with that.
Don't play the games of being LGBTQ when you're not.
It's not a good look.
Trashah has been a-